Our biggest fundraiser
of the year starts today.
Every year, I ask you to help us
‘fill the carrot’ with your donations.
For the fifth year in a row,
an amazing donor has stepped forward
and is providing a substantial match,
so if you make your contribution early,
you can have it doubled.
If you've been part of the NutritionFacts
community for a long time,
you know that my passion for
nutrition and lifestyle medicine
was inspired by my grandmother's
recovery from heart disease.
That's why I do what I do
and why our public health
nonprofit does what it does.
I hear from people every single day
about how their lives were changed
by the information found here
for free at NutritionFacts.org.
Please help us continue and even
expand our work and our reach
to get this life-changing,
life-saving information
in front of as many
people as possible.
We do not accept advertisements
or corporate sponsorships;
we're totally free.
We don't sell you kitchen gadgets,
or supplements, or god knows.
We just want you to live
the longest, healthiest life.
I'd be honored to
receive your support.
Please consider making a
tax-deductible donation today.
On behalf of everyone at NutritionFacts,
staff and volunteers alike, thank you.